Guide to the Herbert F. Janick Jr. Papers MS 012
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
- Series 3: Subject Files, 38885
  - Connecticut
    - Connecticut's Working Class in the 1950s: A Catholic Perspective, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 11)